Muhammad Arif Fathah Wijaya

Bekasi, West Java, 17424 | +62 822 1102 4365 | ariffathahwijaya@gmail.com Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/arif-wijaya

About Me

Honors graduate in Computer Engineering Major Telkom University with experience as a Technical Consultant Analyst at PT Mitra Integrasi Informatika. A communicative, attention to detail, and active listener person. Field of Interest: Software Engineer, Code, Database, Technology, and IoT.

Education

Telkom University

Bandung, Indonesia

Bachelor Degree in Computer Engineering - GPA 3,16

August 2020

- Achieved the following scores on the EPRT Test (English Test) with a Total Score: 517
- Member of Robotic And Embbeded System Laboratory as Admin and Lab Assistant.
- Active on Organization and responsible in many activities
- Final Task Title: Implementation of Hydroponic Plant Maintenance Automatization System With Internet of Things

Skills & Competencies

Java | C# | C | SQL | Database | WebMethods | SoftwareAG | JSON | API | Embedded System | Performance Test | Analytical Thinking | Problem Solving | Public Speaking

Work Experiences

PT Mitra Integrasi Informatika

Jakarta, Indonesia

Technical Consultant Analyst

January 2021-January 2023

- Created and developed service.
- Fixing bug
- Employed Software and other technology to make service and optimize corporate presence
- Deploy and maintain service to Production Server

Dinas Komunikasi Informatika Jawa Barat

Bandung, Indonesia May 2019-July 2019

Built Web Repository as Front End Web

Analyst used technology for all Government web in West Java

Pos Indonesia Bekasi

Bekasi, Indonesia

May 2018-July 2018

Participated in many roles like accounting, logistic, input data, etc.

Leadership & Activities

Kejar Mimpi Bekasi (Volunteer)

Bekasi, Indonesia

Bandung, Indonesia

Program Division

September 2020 – February 2021

- Make a timeline activitiy Build program event
- Robotic and Embedded System Technology

Admin and Assistant Lab

January 2019 - January 2020

Managing Lab Activity as Admin

- Responsibilities to teaching Design Sistem Digital and Mikroprosesor dan Antarmuka
- Manage Practicum and Evaluation the practicum
- Doing research on lab in Embedded System, Robotic, And VLSI

Overclock 2018 - 2019

Bandung, Indonesia

Head of Event Division

October 2018-September 2019

Responsible to lead event division to schedule, managing, and concept the event in Computer Engineering student orientation.

Projects Experiences

Interface Application BI-FAST Bank BJB

August 2021 - March 2022

- The implementation of the Integrated Core System is by applying the Integration Platform technology which consists of the Enterprise Service Bus (ESB)
- Developing service
- Performance Test with output Throught Per Second (TPS) on Apache Jmeter

Implementation Integration Platform Of ESB LPS

June 2021 - September 2021

- The implementation of the Integrated Core System is by applying the Integration Platform technology which consists of the Enterprise Service Bus (ESB)
- Developing service
- Performance test with output Throught Per Second (TPS) on Apache JMeter
- Integrating SAP, harePoint, JDBC adapter to ESB

Migration to SAP With WebMethods Of Pelindo 2

August 2022- recent

- Developing service to migrate SAP Integrating SAP, JDBC adapter to ESB